八个世纪以前 一场鲜为人知的世仇血战  在处于统治地位的吸血鬼与大批叛变的狼人之间展开
传说中 战争是从不死族的长老  亚历山大·柯文纳斯的两个不死之子开始的
被蝙蝠咬伤的马库斯成为了吸血鬼之父
被恶狼咬伤的威廉成为了第一个最强壮的狼人
(公元1202年)
天哪 兄弟你都做了些什么啊？
My God.Brother, what have you done?
我们又一次目睹了这个野兽的暴行
Yet again we arrive to witness this monster's aftermath.
我不能再这样忍受下去了 马库斯
I will not tolerate this any longer, Marcus.
必须阻止你的兄弟
Your brother must be stopped.
从今晚开始
It ends tonight.
在他们变身之前 我们得快点行动
We must move quickly, before they turn.
他仍在这儿吗？
Is he still here?
是的
Yes.
维克多 我们不能伤害他
Viktor, he must not be harmed.
我不是答应过你了吗？
I gave you my word, did I not?
但威廉必须被控制住
But William must be controlled.
烧光尸体
Burn the bodies.
搜索整个区域
Search the outbuildings.
分成两组 你给他们浇上油...
Form two groups.You, douse them with fuel...
马库斯！
Marcus.
留在我身边
Stay with me.
给我火把
Give me the torch.
他们变身了！
They're turning!
退到森林里去
Retreat to the woods.
我要留下来作战 你需要我的帮助
I'll stay and fight.You need my help.
我需要你活着
I need you alive.
如果你死了 我们全都活不成
If you die, we all die.
立刻走！
Now, go.
走！
Go!
找到他了
We found him.
在哪？
And?
我们需要更多人手
We need more men.
去找阿米莉亚
Find Amelia.
阿米莉亚 找到威廉了
Amelia, we found William.
围住他
Surround him!
抓住
Take him down.
不！
No.
放开他！
Leave him be.
住手 会杀死他的
Stop this, you're killing him.
加大力量
More!
威廉
William.
马库斯
Marcus!
不能伤害他
He was not to be harmed.
按照我们的约定 把他交给我
Place him in my charge as we agreed
否则你会为欺骗而付出代价
or you will pay for your deceit.
你要学会一件事
And you will learn your place.
你对这头野兽的同情简直是愚蠢透了
Your sympathy for this beast is foolish.
你兄弟已经完全失控了
Your brother is entirely beyond control.
必须按照我的方法解决
It will be done my way.
你很清楚杀死我或是威廉 结果是一样的
You know well the consequences if you murder me or William.
如果你再提他的名字
If you so much as speak his name again
我就把他碎尸万段
you will have chosen that future for him.
你要怎样处置他 主人？
What is thy will, my lord?
将他终身囚禁
Lmprisonment for all time.
离你越远越好
Far from you.
六个世纪以来 我一直是吸血鬼家族的忠实斗士
For six centuries I was a loyal soldier of the Vampire clan.
但我遭到背叛
But I was betrayed.
这场战争并不像表面看起来那样
The war was not as it had seemed.
一夜之间
In one night,
我们联合在一起的谎言被揭穿了
the lies that had united our kind had been exposed.
克莱恩 是第二个领导者
Kraven, our second-in-command
和卢西恩建立了秘密的联盟
had formed a secret alliance with Lucian
狼人的领导者
ruler of the Werewolf clan
想推翻我们领导人维克多的统治
to overthrow Viktor, our leader.
但克莱恩的野心计划 最终以失败而告终
But Kraven's lust for power and domination had failed.
维克多也并非我想象中的救世主
Viktor was not the saviour I had been led to believe.
他背叛了我的家人
He had betrayed us all.
不久 大家便开始找寻杀死他的凶手
Soon the hunt will be on for his killer.
我仅有一个同伴
I have but one ally left.
迈克尔
Michael
柯文纳斯的人类后裔
the human descendant of Corvinus.
既非吸血鬼也非狼人
Neither Vampire nor Lycan
而是混血
but a hybrid.
我们被找到是迟早的事
It's only a matter of time before we're found.
《黑夜传说2:进化》
我现在唯一的希望就是唤醒马库斯
My only hope now is to awaken Marcus
我们最后的一个长者
our last remaining elder
并告知他真相
and expose the truth
我们必须抢在克莱恩趁他休眠杀死他之前
before Kraven tries to murder him while he's still in hibernation.
克莱恩知道他一旦苏醒 自己就死定了
Kraven knows he's no match for him awake.
棒极了
Perfect.
他已死好几周了
This thing's been dead for weeks.
我记得狼人死后会变成人形
I thought Lycans went back to their human form when they die.
确实如此
They do.
但他被注射了防退变的药物
This one's been given a serum to stop regression
以做实验研究
so it can be studied.
你怎么知道的？
How can you tell?
(标本被注射了850毫升试剂：以防退化)
我认为 这不太像你的专长
Not quite your department, I guess.
我只杀他们
I just killed them.
不会去研究他们
I didn't pay much attention to their anatomy.
我们能呆多久？
How long can we stay here?
不久
Not long.
这些房间全都连接在主控网上
These safe houses are all linked together on one mainframe
动作传感器会探知哪里有活动
with motion sensors revealing which ones are active.
或许我们已经被发现了
Someone could have picked us up already.
还有一小时天就亮了
There's only about an hour till daylight.
能在天亮前赶回来吗？
Can you even make it back to the mansion before sunrise?
刚刚好
Just.
好吧 咱们拿上东西就走
Okay, let's get what we need and go.
不
No.
我要一个人去
I'm going alone.
打开
Open it.
马库斯？
Marcus?
这肮脏的血液中储存的记忆
The blood memories of this wretched creature,
已经告诉我你的无耻背叛
have shown me that your treachery knows no bounds.
主人 听我解释
My lord, I can explain.
我为什么要听你的谎言
Why would I listen to your lies
探知真相的途径
when the journey to the truth
将是无比的甜美？
is so much sweeter?
我替他保守秘密
I kept his secrets,
收拾残局
cleaned up the mess.
你要在维克多面前
You'll go before Viktor
把我对你说的一字不差的告诉他
and tell him exactly what I tell you to!
你只要尽好自己的本分就是了
You just concentrate on your part.
求求你
Please.
我能够协助你
I can assist you.
你能做的都已做了
Oh, you already have.
如果能申诉成功
If I can plead my case,
你或许会被带到庇护所
there's a chance you'll be granted sanctuary
现在 你会被当场击毙
Right now, you'll be killed on sight.
我不会让你冒险的
I'm not prepared to risk it.
那我干嘛 坐在这等你吗？
So what am I supposed to do, sit and wait for you?
不 克莱恩仍有很多手下
No, Kraven may still have his men with him.
你不能自己去
You're not going alone.
你并没有自己想象得那么强壮
You're not as strong as you might think.
什么？
What?
迈克尔 你是独一无二的
Michael, you're unique.
之前 从未有过混血儿
There's never been a hybrid before.
然而 你也会为此而感到矛盾
However ambivalent you might feel about it,
事实上 你的力量是无法估量的
the truth is your powers could be limitless.
但你必须依靠血液
But you depend on blood.
血液是你的食物
You need to feed.
没有血液 你会逐渐变得虚弱
Without it, you'll be growing weaker,
不需多久 就会验证的
by the second.Use the time for that.
老天！
Jesus Christ.
如果我不需要？
And what if I don't?
我不依靠血液呢？
What if I can't?
普通的食物会使你丧命
Normal food could be lethal.
如果不能控制自己 你会攻击人类
If you don't anticipate your cravings, you will attack humans.
相信我 你不会想失去理智的
And believe me, you don't want that on your conscience.
真的是不能再回头了 迈克尔
There really is no going back, Michael.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道你所做的一切
Look, I understand what you did.
我很感激
I'm grateful.
你救了我一命
You saved my life.
对于死亡 我还没有心理准备
I wasn't ready to die.
我不知道
I don't know.
一切都变得太快了
Everything's changed.
或许我需要点时间仔细想一想
I probably need just a minute to make it all fit in my head.
突然发生的这一切
It's a lot to process all at once.
听着 去吧
Look, go.
我会在这的等你
I'll be here.
只要保证你能够安全回来
You just make sure you come back.
长官
Sir.
那些目击者...
The innocent who witnessed...
他们知道些什么吗？
they've been silenced?
按您命令 他们什么都不清楚
But otherwise unharmed, as ordered.
给我看你的情报
Show me what you have.
好的 长官
Yes, sir.
两个死亡行者被杀
Two Death Dealers were killed.
我们没发现狼人的尸体
We found no Lycan bodies.
很显然 使用了一种新式武器
Apparently they were using a new kind of ammunition,
好像是某种紫外弹
some sort of UV round.
阿米莉亚呢？
Amelia?
没有幸存者
No one survived.
看上去 好像克莱恩的手下也在场
It seems Kraven's men might have been present,
但好像没有去阻止
but they did nothing to prevent it.
维克多呢？
And Viktor?
残局里没有马库斯的痕迹吗？
And no trace of Marcus amongst the ashes?
他好像毁掉了自己的家
It seems he destroyed his own coven, sir.
那从来就不是他的家
It was never his coven.
我们得快走
We need to go.
让我独自呆会儿
Give me a moment.
找到你了！
There you are.
你好！
How you doing?
谢谢！
Thank you.
迈克尔·柯文...
Michael Corvin...
离我远一点
You've got to get away from me.
快滚开
Get away from me!
在那！
There.
立刻派人过去
Get the men up there.Now.
他妈的给我滚开
Get the fuck away from me.
该死！
Shit.
迈克尔
Michael.
来 快喝
Here.Take it.
不
No.
迈克尔 你会死的
Michael, you'll die.
妈的！
Shit.
你能动吗？
Can you move?
我们必须躲起来
We need to go.
马库斯
Marcus.
我知道你做了些什么 瑟琳娜
I know what you've done, Selene.
维克多该死 克莱恩也是一样
Viktor deserved his fate and Kraven was no better.
克莱恩已得到了应有的下场
Kraven has already reaped the rewards of his own misdeeds.
至于维克多
And Viktor,
维克多死多少次都是活该
Viktor deserved his fate, many times over.
一个骇人听闻的交易
A terrible business,
他对你家人的残酷杀戮
the slaying of your family.
还费尽心思想对我隐瞒事实
Yet so much effort was spent to conceal this matter from me.
维克多到底在隐瞒什么呢？
What do you suppose Viktor had to hide?
或许是你吧 瑟琳娜
Or perhaps it is you, Selene
隐藏你这个悲惨家族中的最后一员
as the last of your wretched family
有什么事情瞒着我
who has something to hide.
快走！
Go!
那是什么鬼东西？
是否介意我来开？
上车
Get in.
无论如何  我必将得到我想要的东西
Dead or alive, you will give me what I want.
你没事吧？
You okay?
他可真是个狗杂种？
He's a hybrid, isn't he?
没错
Yes.
他想要这东西 为什么？
He wanted this.Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们还有麻烦
But we have another problem.
从这边过去
Turn off up here.
该死！
Shit.
快点 趴下
All right, get down.
踩住油门 趴下
Keep your foot on the gas, but stay down.
坚持住
Hold on.
趴着
Stay down.
来吧
Come on.
手伸出来
Give me your hand.
老天！
Jesus Christ.
不要紧的
There's really no need.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
好了 让我看看
All right, let me see.
瞧？
See?
没事了
No need.
他们不在这里 长官
Area secure, sir.
日落了
Sun's setting.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
弹药都被拿走了 留下的只有一些武器
The supplies were taken.Used weapons were left behind.
他们在日出前离开
The tavern events occurred just before dawn,
所以 他们走不远
so they couldn't have got very far.
继续搜索
Remain airborne for the moment.
我确信他们会再次出现的
I'm sure they'll reappear in good time.
好的 长官
Yes, sir.
我小时候见过这个东西
I've seen this before, when I was a child.
当时我拿在手里
I've held it.
就像这样打开它
When it was open, like this.
怎么可能？
How is that possible?
我也不知道
I don't know.
但有一个人或许知道
But I know someone that might.
安德里亚斯·泰尼斯
Andreas Tanis.
他是联盟中的史学家
He was the official historian of the covens.
他喜欢收录被
He fell from favour after documenting what
维克多认为的恶毒谎言 所以失宠了
Viktor considered malicious lies.
当然 后来发现诸多记载确有其事
Of course, as it turns out, he was probably telling the truth.
他现在怎么样？
What happened to him?
他三百年前被流放了
He was exiled over 300 years ago.
三百年了？
300 years?
你怎么肯定我们现在能找到他？
What makes you think we're gonna find him now?
他是被我押送流放的
I was the one who exiled him.
看起来像是修道院
Looks like a monastery.
以前是 现在是一所监狱
It used to be.More like a prison now.
自维克多下令后 泰尼斯就一直被关在这里
Tanis has been hiding there since Viktor's order.
我们将是这几世纪以来 第一个拜访他的人
We'll be the first people he's seen in centuries.
奇怪？
That's odd.
怎么？
What?
我不记得有这扇门
I don't remember this gate being here before.
拿着这个
Take this.
(警告：内有猎犬)
该死
Shit.
退后！
Go back!
抓住了
Gotcha.
妈的！
Fuck.
我就知道是你 瑟琳娜
I knew it was you, Selene.
你的血液仍散发着维克多的腥臭味
The stench of Viktor's blood still lingers in your veins.
泰尼斯
Tanis.
我看你瞄准的功夫没什么长进
I see your aim hasn't improved.
你一点都没变
You haven't changed.
我不怕你 瑟琳娜
You don't scare me, Selene.
看来 我还要继续努力啊
Well, we're gonna have to work on that.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
你的流放生活比我记忆中好得多
Your exile seems a bit more comfortable than I remember.
什么时候吸血鬼开始雇佣狼人当保镖了？
How does a Vampire have Lycan bodyguards?
一件礼物
A gift.
来自一个很有说服力的客户
From a most persuasive client.
卢西恩
Lucian.
为什么卢西恩要保护你？
Why would Lucian wanna protect you?
因为他们之间有交易
Because he was trading with them.
紫外弹
UV rounds.
你以残杀自己的族人为交易有多久了？
How long have you been in the business of killing your own kind?
我做的一切都是为了生存
I've done what's necessary to survive.
我决心要安定生活的时候 你敬重的维克多背叛了我
My decision was made easy the day your precious Viktor betrayed me.
背叛可是他的专长
Betrayal was something he did very well.
维克多死了 我杀了他
Viktor's dead.I killed him.
你？
You?
杀了维克多？
Kill Viktor?
不 我才不信呢
No, I think not.
哦 除非你知道真相的话
Oh, unless you've learned the truth.
哦...
Ah...
你终于知道了
So your eyes are finally open.
隐藏的真相甚至比谎言更难以接受
Isn't it interesting how the truth is even harder to absorb than light?
当然 你要知道 我试图想劝说他
You know, I tried to stop him, of course.
很滑稽 他犯下了这样的罪行
A travesty, committing such a horrible crime.
竟然瞒过了你
And then turning you.
他做得太过份了
That was too much to take.
我反对他的做法 所以被关在这里
My protests are why he put me here.
小心一点 亲爱的
Careful with that, dear.
那东西威力很大
Makes a terrible bang.
打开刀片后就会爆炸
Open the blades and they're active.
太感谢了！
Good to know.
维克多把你关在这一定有他的理由
Viktor put you here for a reason,
但是我怀疑是因为你隐瞒了一些事情
but I doubt it was because you had moral qualms.
你到底知道些什么？
What do you know?
恐怕我什么都不知道
Very little of anything, I'm afraid.
哦
Well,
那是我看走眼了 原来你没有任何利用价值
then, perhaps I'm mistaken and there's no use for you at all.
马库斯想得到这个 为什么？
Marcus was after this.Why?
有些历史是真实的
Some history is based on truth
而有些确实是谎言
and others on deception.
维克多并不是你们所认为的第一个吸血鬼
Viktor was not the first of our kind, as you were led to believe.
他以前是个人类
He was once human
统治着一部分土地
the ruler of these lands.
马库斯
Marcus
他是唯一的
he's the one.
源头
The source.
真正的第一个吸血鬼
The first true Vampire.
那传言就是真的了
So the legend is true.
在他奄奄一息的时候
Toward the end of his ruthless life,
对于维克多而言 生命比黄金、白银还要珍贵
when the next breath meant more to Viktor than silver or gold,
马库斯找到了他
Marcus came
告诉他
with an offer,
可以永远摆脱疾病和死亡
a reprieve from sickness and death.
可以获得永生
Immortality.
作为回报 维克多必须率领军队来帮助他
And in return, Viktor was to use his army-turned-immortal to help him.
帮助他什么？
To do what?
控制住第一个狼人
To defeat the very first Werewolves,
他非常危险 并具有极强的感染力
a dangerous and infectious breed
与马库斯有着同样的血统
created by Marcus' own flesh and blood
他的孪生兄弟 威廉
His twin brother, William.
但他和现在的狼人还不一样
But these weren't the Lycans we know.
你的同伴或许很让人厌烦
Disgusting though your brethren may be,
但至少他们进化了
they at least are evolved.
那些狂暴的野兽
No, these were raging monsters.
永远不会再变回人形
Never able to take human form again.
他们的后代学会了如何控制自己的怒火
It was only later generations that learned to channel their rage.
威廉的狂暴与毁灭是永无休止的
And William's appetite for destruction and rampage was insatiable.
因此 必须阻止他
He had to be stopped.
维克多的士兵变成了吸血鬼
And so once Viktor's army was turned,
他率领大批的吸血鬼
the legions of Vampires under his control
追捕和消灭这些野兽
tracked down and destroyed the animals,
还捉住了威廉
then captured William
并把他关在了很远的地方
and locked him away.
永远的被维克多所囚禁
Viktor's prisoner for all time.
为什么要让他活着？
Why let him live?
这与维克多从来都维护马库斯原因一样
For the very same reason that Viktor never conspired against Marcus.
恐惧
Fear.
有人告诫他 马库斯要是死了
He was warned that, should Marcus ever be killed,
所有的吸血鬼都将会随他而亡
all those in his bloodline would follow him to the grave.
因此 在维克多的头脑中
So in Viktor's mind,
威廉兄弟的死将意味着一切都会消失
William's death would mean the end for all Lycans,
因此 他受马库斯的支配
his slaves.
没错
Yes.
一个聪明的谎言
Yes, a clever deception,
而维克多根本不敢冒这个险
but one Viktor was hardly willing to put to the test.
于是他要保护马库斯
And so Marcus was protected
不惜一切代价
at all costs.
哦 没错 找到了
Ah, yes, here we are.
吸血鬼？
Vampires?
人类
Mortals.
与所有人都颇有渊源的亚历山大·柯文纳斯
Men loyal to Alexander Corvinus.
我们所有人的祖先
The father of us all.
这是什么？
What's this?
你应该知道
You should know.
威廉被囚禁的地方
It's William's prison.
你父亲奉命建造的监狱
The prison your father was commissioned to build.
你要为我看护这里 知道吗？
So you've been the one keeping a watch over this for me, have you?
我正在到处找它 亲爱的
I've been searching everywhere for this, my darling.
怎么了？
What is it?
有什么不对吗？
What's wrong?
她终于明白她的家人为何被杀了
She now understands why her family was killed.
但那是多年之后的事
But that was many years later.
就是卢西恩逃脱的那个冬天
The winter of Lucian's escape.
你父亲知道的事情太多
Your father knew too much.
至少对于维克多来说 太多 太危险了
Or too much for Viktor to risk,
尤其当卢西恩
especially when Lucian
拿到威廉的监狱钥匙后
had the key to William's cell.
而我就是囚禁室的地图
And I'm the map.
没错
Yes.
你是唯一知道囚禁室位置的幸存者
The only one still living who has seen its location.
哦...维克多认为你那时太小 还不记事
Oh, Viktor realized you'd be too young to remember explicitly,
但马库斯可以获取
but Marcus knows that the memory,
威廉监狱的确切的位置
and therefore the exact location of William's prison
通过隐藏在你血液里的记忆
is hidden away in your blood.
为什么马库斯现在要找他
Why is Marcus looking for him now
已经过了这么多久了
after all this time?
这我无法回答
That I cannot answer.
不过我知道一个能阻止他的人
But I do know someone who could stop him.
或许我可以安排你们见面
Perhaps I could arrange a meeting.
但你们必须放我一马
In exchange for your discretion, of course.
当然
Of course.
泰尼斯
Tanis.
你好像很不安
You seem anxious.
为什么一看见我就要跑？
Why do you flee the very sight of me?
请...
Please...
坐吧
sit.
你不必这么惧怕我
There's no need for this to be unpleasant.
我对你一直很满意
I've always rather enjoyed your company.
这就不太友善了
Now you're being rude.
对不起
Sorry.
维克多造了两把钥匙
Viktor struck two keys.
你知道它们吗？
What do you know of them?
钥匙？
Keys?
我不知道什么钥匙
I don't know of any keys.
哦 当然
Oh, yes.
是的 你是说那些钥匙
Yes, those keys.
没错
Yes.
嗯 一个...
Well, one was...
放在很明显的地方
One was kept in plain sight,
就戴在他女儿的脖子上
draped around his daughter's neck,
你很容易就能看到
right there for you to see.
另一个呢？
And the other?
维克多一直带着它
Kept with Viktor at all times.
在哪？
Where?
在他的体内
Within him.
藏在皮肉下面
Beneath the flesh.
请 请不要 求你了 别杀我
Please.Please.I beg you.Please.
...可以阻止他的人 或许我可以安排你们见面
...Who could stop him.Perhaps I could arrange a meeting.
到17号码头
Go to pier 17.
找洛伦兹·马卡罗
Ask for Lorenz Macaro.
你怎么知道泰尼斯不是在骗我们
How do we know Tanis isn't setting us up?
他还没有骗我的胆量
He's not brave enough to set me up.
你们闯进了私人领地
慢慢从车里走出来 让我看到你的手
我们来这里找洛伦兹·马卡罗
从车里出来 慢慢的
把手放在我能看见的地方
你想看我的手是吗？
你们可以下去了
You can go.
你好像很熟悉这东西？
You're familiar with this, then?
非常熟悉
Intimately.
你是亚历山大·柯文纳斯
You're Alexander Corvinus.
有一段时间是用过这个名字
There was a time that I was known by that name.
无论什么名字 我始终是你的祖先
By any name, I am still your forefather.
这么多世纪 你是如何藏匿行踪的？
How have you stayed hidden all these years?
几世纪以来 眼看着
For centuries I've stood by and watched the havoc
我子孙后代间的争斗
my sons have wrought upon each other
以及对人类的伤害
and upon humanity.
我祈求这不是我造成的
Not the legacy I prayed for
我看着他们凌晨进入这个世界
the morning I watched them enter this world.
我已经厌倦了这个工作
And a tiresome duty
遏制争斗 清理残局
keeping the war contained, cleaning up the mess,
隐藏家族悲惨的历史
hiding my family's unfortunate history.
你怎么不阻止呢？
Couldn't you have stopped it?
是啊
Yes.
你们能杀死你的儿子吗？
Could you kill your own sons?
你知道马库斯要做什么
You know what Marcus will do.
如果他找到我 也就找到囚禁威廉地方
If he finds me, he finds William's prison.
你必须帮我们阻止他
You need to help us stop him.
你要我帮你杀死我儿子
You are asking me to help you kill my son.
你？
You?
一个死亡行者？
A Death Dealer?
在六个世纪里 你杀了多少无辜的人
How many innocents did you kill in the six-century
为了替你的家族复仇
quest to avenge your family?
别跟我讲什么正义宣言
Spare me your self-righteous declarations.
你与马库斯没什么区别
You are no different from Marcus
甚至还不如威廉
and even less noble than William.
至少他无法控制自己的怒火
At least he cannot control his savagery.
我的所作所为都是因你而起的
Anything I've done can be laid at your feet.
几十万无辜的人被杀 都因你
Hundreds of thousands have died because of
接受不了
your inability to accept that
你两个儿子均是怪物的事实
your sons are monsters.
而他们还制造出更多的怪物
that they create monsters.
你完全可以阻止这一切的发生
You could've stopped all of this.
别以为你可以在这对我指手画脚...
Do not come grovelling to me simply
就因为你比对手弱
because you are weaker than your adversary.
你也看到了威廉所酿成的惨状
You know the devastation William caused
在没被囚禁起来以前
before he was captured.
他不能被放出来
He cannot be set free.
不 等一等
No, wait.
你根本无法与他对抗
You're no match for him.
就快了 兄弟
Soon, brother.
不
No.
父亲
Father.
不
No.
他们已经死了 我的孩子
They've gone.there, my child.
你现在安全了
You are safe now.
不 迈克尔
No.Michael.
看着我
Look at me.
迈克尔
Michael.
该死！
Shit.
不要
Please.
求你了
快点
Come on.
醒过来
妈的
Fuck.
你好 父亲
Hello, Father.
我这里不欢迎你
You are unwelcome in my presence.
啊
Ah.
一颗可以预知未来、永不停止的心脏
The predictable heart that never thaws.
可惜在愚蠢人的体内跳动
Pity it beats within such a fool.
不死族中最年长的长老
The eldest of the immortals,
却从未尝试掌握自己的命运
yet you have made no attempt to seize your destiny.
你和我都是异类 仅此而已
We are oddities of nature, you and I.Nothing more.
这是属于人类的世界
This is a world for humanity.
这就是你对抛弃亲生骨肉而做出的无聊解释吗？
And that petty sentiment explains why you rejected your sons?
这就是在过去六个世纪里 你眼看着
Why you stood by for over half a millennium
威廉独自在黑暗中受尽折磨的原因吗？
as William suffered alone in darkness?
不 父亲
No, Father.
我无法理解你那套无聊的情感
I have no respect for your petty sentiment.
维克多的钥匙
Viktor's key.
在哪里？
Where is it?
无论什么计划 你都不要对威廉抱有任何幻想
Whatever plan you have for William is futile.
你无法控制他
You cannot control your brother.
哦 我现在强壮了
Oh, I am stronger now.
我们俩的关系
And our bond is
远比你所想象的要好
greater than you have ever wanted to acknowledge.
你错了
You're wrong.
很快你就会淹没在狼人的海洋中 就像以前一样
Soon you'll be drowning in Lycans, just like before.
哦 不会有狼人 父亲...
Oh, not Lycans, Father...
或者吸血鬼
or Vampires.
一个全新的种族
A new race,
将被他们的缔造者所创建
created in the image of their maker
一个新的上帝
their new god
我
Me.
一个真正的上帝
And a true god
是没有父亲的
has no father.
你终将要失败
You will fail.
快拿医药箱
Get the kit.
不
No.
请不要 长官
Please, sir,
让我们救你
let us help you.
时辰到了 我的朋友
The time has come, my friend.
去找那个女孩
Find the girl.
带她来见我
Bring her to me.
不 等等 等一下
No, wait.Wait.
你如果想对付马库斯 就需要亚历山大的帮助
If you want Marcus, you'll need Alexander's help.
不要把他留在这里
Don't leave him here.
他得到你那把钥匙了？
Did he get the pendant?
是的
Yes.
对于你来说他太强壮了
He's too powerful for you alone.
你是唯一比他年长
You are the only one older than he is,
唯一比他强壮的人
the only one stronger.
你可以亲手杀了他
You could have killed him yourself.
不管他变成什么样...
No matter what he's become...
他终究是我的儿子
he is my son.
你是最后的希望了
You are the last hope left.
只有一种方法可以击败他
There is only one way to defeat him.
快点 现在
Quickly, now,
趁我血液里的遗留物还没有消散以前
before there is no more legacy left in my veins.
我会变成什么？
What will I become?
未来
The future.
现在去吧
Go now.
我们已经接近了
We're getting close.
调头 绕到河那边
Head back around towards the river.
我没看到有任何入口
I don't see a way inside.
以前在那有个入口
There used to be a river entrance just there.
现在一定是被淹没了
It must be submerged now.
看来得游过去了
Looks like we're getting wet.
靠近点
Closer.
瑟琳娜
Selene.
威廉
William.
等等
Wait.
不 威廉 停下
No, William.Stop.
我们是兄弟
Be still, brother
是我
It's me.
伤害你就等于伤害我自己
I'd no sooner harm you than myself.
哪条路？
Which way?
是这里吗？
Is this it?
他已经到了
He's already here.
那是什么？
What is that?
没什么
Nothing.
我们走
Let's go
我们来迟一步
We're too late.
追上去 跟在后面
After him.Get behind him.
真不可思议
Impressive.
迈克尔 你是独一无二的
Michael, you're unique.
之前 从未有过混血儿
There's never been a hybrid before.
你的力量是无法估量的
Your powers could be limitless.
别开火
Hold it!
哦 妈的
Oh, fuck.
他在哪里？
Where is he?
他从那边过去了
He went right through there.
我们仅有紫外弹 对他不起作用
All we have are UV rounds.They won't take him down.
的确不能 但能减缓他的速度
No, but they'll slow him down.
我们走
Let's go.
你没事吧？
You all right?
老天！
Jesus Christ!
但他和现在的狼人还不一样
But these weren't the Lycans we know.
那些狂暴的野兽
No, these were raging monsters.
永远不会再变回人形
Unable to take human form ever again.
你在等什么？
What are you waiting for?
快开枪
Shoot them.
不行 我会伤到她
I can't.Not without taking her out.
我无法瞄准目标
I can't get a shot.
迈克尔
Michael.
干掉他
Take her down.
切断缆绳！
Cut us loose!
我们要坠毁了
We're going down!
威廉！
William!
我知道 维克多留下你当作宠物是个错误
I knew Viktor made a mistake by keeping you as a pet.
他应该把你和你的家人一起杀了
He should have killed you with the rest of your family.
一个无法预知的未来
An unknown chapter lies ahead.
随着族群间的界限日趋模糊
The lines that had divided the clans have now been blurred.
混乱和杀戮是在所难免
Chaos and infighting are inevitable.
唯一确定的就是我们仍将面对黑暗
All that is certain is that darkness is still ahead.
然而在此时
But for now,
第一次
for the first time.
我在曙光中看到了希望...
I look into the light with new hope...